this is the time known as the great pirate era a countless array of pirates go to battle across
the seas in search of the one piece the legendary treasure left behind by gold roger king of the
pirates monkey d luffy a boy whose body turned to rubber after eating the gum gum fruit set sail to
become the next king of the pirates as luffy and his crew conquer numerous obstacles they capture
the unwanted attention of the world government which will use any means necessary to stop them
can't wait to see what kind of adventures up next with a charted course awash in danger and intrigue
the crew will cut a path across the grand line to the new world
separated from the rest of the straw hat crew luffy is headed toward navy hq with his new cohorts
ivankov jimbae buggy crocodile and more all in order to save his brother ace meanwhile the other
straw hats are busy as well your combat outfit huh and i fell for it too oh you look cute shut up i do not
what the hell why can't i land a single attack i'm only trying to show you that you have doubt in your
heart shut up you don't know what you're talking about oh don't i
dear nami and robin how are you i hope this finds you well i do so look forward to seeing the two of
you again i'm certain that when the time comes we'll be better friends than ever before
right there i see reindeer
you're kidding me they've got us cornered
awesome are you guys really coming to help us
i guess she must be the mother
the friends whereabouts revolutionaries and the gorging forests trap
so how are you liking those sea prism stone armlets we got you
well it just goes to show some men have no taste when it comes to giving a lady a gift
cut the crap where can i find the rest of the straw hat crew
if you're trying to seduce me you've got a lot to learn about setting the mood
talk damn you
nico robin last thing we need's that troublemaker raising hell around here
rumor has it she sank six vessels when she was only eight years old
and something tells me she's not the type to accept a life in prison
if she managed to break out she could overturn our entire country in no time at all
we have to keep her identity a secret i can't let the insurgents get their hands on her
excuse me sir
what is it
well it's in regards to the delays to construction
double the laborers hours and scale back to one meal a day
that should help to make up for the lost time
but sir i've been receiving more and more reports lately of growing dissent among the laborers
we shouldn't be too harsh on them
i'm not worried about the damn peasants
there aren't even enough of them to pull off a coup
the only real threat facing us now is nico rob
i actually what i meant to say is that the laborers are expendable and you need to start treating them that way
who said you can stop pull harder
get the lead out of your butt can't you see we're hungry
old man hey are you okay
what are you wasting your time for
jesus dying just leave him to rot
hey are you dead for something
hey why'd you guys stop working
all right
stupid rubes go on and get back to your posts
if you don't feel like working i'd be happy to send you to the prison tower instead
there's nothing worse than the prison tower
that poor lady
we know how much you like seawater so go on and drink it up
you forgot to chill at first
we're set to make a fortune off you
and all we have to do is hand you over to a navy ship
even if you're nothing but a cadaver
i bet your mother's so proud
what did you say
lucky us another delicious serving of potato skin soup
how are we supposed to work on a diet like this
a token of thanks for your cooperation
here enjoy some chocolate
thank you you're too kind
filthy informant
i just did it to survive and it's all mine damn it
hey wait
you can't have any
just forget her
you realize what she did don't you
remember that nice lady you tried to take in and save
while she's in the prison tower because of her
i know she's right
but that lady gave herself up in order to save us
i should try to be as strong as she is
and i bet she'd forgive her
what are you doing here
i won't share
all i wanted was to get out of here
and i don't feel sorry for what i've done
all right fine
uh thank you i knew that you were really a nice person
i'm sorry but i was just so scared
our lives are completely hopeless
we're stuck on this bridge
we do nothing but suffer till the day we finally die
you know i still haven't thanked that lady for saving us
so this chocolate
i'll give it to her
move faster
get back to work
here's your breakfast lunch and dinner
once you finish that we'll get back to our questioning
oh i can hardly wait
not to intrude
but it sounds like you've been hurt pretty bad young lady
who
just a decrepit old man
i've only been in this country for a single day now
but the guards in charge said the elderly are useless
so they promptly threw me in here
i'm so sorry to hear that
but i know how you feel
i can't waste any more time in this country
i have to get out of here
even if it means cutting off my own arms
my dear lady
don't do anything so drastic
perk up your ears for a moment
do you hear that
me
don't do anything so grin
Something wrong?
What the?
There's a band of dissidents running wild.
The warden called for backup.
He ordered all of us to get over there.
Sir!
Hey, lady!
Can you hear me?
I know she's here, but where?
Hello?
Sorin!
There you are!
I wanted to thank you for helping us!
What are you doing?
A band of dissidents?
Yes, sir.
But we were quick to follow your orders, sir.
All teams descended on the group so it didn't get out of hand.
What are you talking about?
I didn't give any orders!
Don't tell me.
When you say all teams, do you mean the soldiers stationed at the prison tower?
Hey!
Sorin!
How did you get in here?
I'm an agent working for the Revolutionary Army.
Are you all right?
The diversion went perfectly.
Then good work.
With your command of our forces, I know we can win.
Well, you can count on me.
Oh, before we go, release the young lady from her cell.
She's already been through enough as it is.
It looks like it's your lucky day.
Thanks.
I appreciate it.
You fool!
You really think I give a damn about the dissidents?
Take down Miko Robin on site, men!
This one doesn't fit either.
Just to warn you, things will get a little messy for a while.
It'd be in your best interest to find some place where you can hide.
I'm afraid you'd only slow us down if you stick with us.
Already?
Oh, no.
Miko Robin.
Kill her!
And Kutch!
I owe you all a debt of gratitude.
And I'll fight beside you to pay it back.
Miko Robin is free at attacking our men.
No!
Please help me!
She broke out.
And now she's coming.
It's all over.
Everything is over.
Miko Robin!
You have a nice name.
Hm.
Hey, Luffy.
Luffy, you really need to try to get some rest, if only a little.
Yeah, thank you, but I'm okay.
The wind's died down entirely.
We do still have the current pulling us forward, but there's more than a good chance we might
not arrive in time.
Hey, Luffy.
No, there's no point in making him any more anxious.
He's got enough to worry about.
The kid's about to dive headfirst into an unimaginable war.
Hang on, Ace.
It's a giant man-eating sunflower!
Yes, it is!
And my name is Heraclesin!
Heraclesin!
Help me!
Her...
I said help!
I'm sick of hearing your stupid name!
Whaaaaat?
You're depressed?
Sleep depressed?
Help me, Heracles!
Your name's not stupid!
It's perfect for a hero of the forest!
Huh?
Hero of the forestin?
Of course you're the hero!
Just look how cool and strong you are!
Indeed, I am the hero of the forestin!
Heraclesin!
Oh, wow!
You're even cooler than I thought!
Rusopin!
Here I come!
Help me, Heracles!
Get ready!
Please, Heracles!
Heracles!
Whoa!
I'm still alive.
Why do these monster plants only want to attack me?
Only the fit survive here.
You've got to stay alert and have stamina.
And you're the weakest creature on this island.
Even the ants in and worms in are stronger than you.
Hey, screw you.
I may be weak, but I'm stronger than a bunch of ants and worms.
Hungry?
Oh, not for that.
You've got to eat if you want to build up your stamina and strength.
Yeah, trust me.
I'm starving.
But there's nothing on this island I really feel comfortable eating.
Oh, but I wish there was.
I think I might know of something.
We've been walking forever.
You sure there's food up here?
Yeah.
The best food on the island.
It smells so good.
Oh, and eat bugs when you've got stuff like this.
Ramen falls in.
Spaghetti patches in.
Ham fruits in.
Chocolate rocks in.
Take whatever you want.
It's all safe to eat.
Ow.
So I'm okay to eat this too, right?
Right.
Yum, yum.
Eat your fill.
Once you've had enough to build up your stamina, the man eating plants in won't mess with you.
Sure, right.
Good plan.
This stuff is so good.
But I feel like I could eat forever.
Eating's only the first step.
You've got to exercise too.
Well, yeah, obviously.
But I'm still on the first step here.
I've got to bulk up so I can become a cool hero of the forest like you, right?
You want to become a hero like me?
We're the heroes of the forest.
Periclesen!
Oh, Usoppin.
Huh?
Usoppin?
Where'd you go?
Wow!
It's all so good!
I can't stop eating this stuff.
That way.
I don't even care that I'm full.
It's just too delicious.
Usoppin!
Where are you?
You're going to be an even bigger target if you eat too much.
Oh, I should stop.
But I can't control my hands.
Finally, I found you.
What do you think, Heracles?
Seems like the proper amount of bulk to become a hero, right?
What have you done to yourself?
That's the wrong kind of bulk, you fool.
You better burn some calories right this instant or you're going to be in big trouble.
What's that, an earthquake?
It's beginning.
Holy crap, that is a huge mouth!
Please don't fall!
Don't fall!
Seven!
Heracles!
Don't let go!
Too heavy!
Goodbye, Usoppin!
So this is how I died!
Oh, Robin!
What a world!
Oh, man!
I can't eat another bite!
I don't want an illusion!
Zappin!
Oh man, I can't eat another bite.
Ooh, Zappin.
Don't you realize fat things are the first creatures to be eaten on this island?
Wait, are you talking about me?
It's impossible to escape from the Bowen Islands!
Why didn't you tell me that before?
As for me, I'm the hero of the forest!
Zoro wanders a spooky island trying to reunite with his friends.
Thwarted by his poor sense of direction, Perona, and mysterious adversaries, his odds do not look good.
Meanwhile, Brook gets to see some underwear before his troubles truly begin.
On the next One Piece, the friend's whereabouts, a huge tomb and a panty debt, I'm gonna be king of the pirates!